[{"answer": "yeah, well, the days of me forgittin' are over, and the days of me rememberin' have just begun", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I sound like a sensible fucking man, is what I sound like", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "When you go on like this, you know what you sound like", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "You sound like a duck.  Quack, quack, quack, quack, quack, quack, quack..", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I don't know. There probably never was a little girl  the point of the story isn't the little girl. The point of the story is they robbed the bank with a telephone", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I'm not sayin' I wanna rob banks, I'm just illustrating that if we did, it would be easier than what we been doin'", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "You wanna rob banks", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "So you don't want to be a bank robber", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Yes we did", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "A lot of wallets", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Examples", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "They don't call it a Quarter Pounder with Cheese", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "my friend with Cheese", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "that place's a that place, but they call it Le that place", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " my friend with Cheese. What'd they call a Big Mac", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Le Big Mac. What do they call a Whopper", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Well what then", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "A foot massage", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "my friend. Why you so interested in big man's wife", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Take care of her", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "This is my friend's. my friend man should love it", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "You can get a steak here, dadd", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "How 'bout you, my friend", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "How d'ya want that shake, my friend and my friend, or my friend and my friend", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Sure did. I heard you did a pilot", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "What was it", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Then let's just forget it", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Is that a fact", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "It's ready, I'll tell you what to do", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "No, you're gonna give her the shot", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "You killed the other boxing man", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "The radio said he was dead", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "...my friend  is that Mexican", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "It's a very pretty name", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "U", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "You were lookin' in the mirror and you wish you had some pot", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "I wish I had a pot", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "A pot. A pot belly. Pot bellies are sexy", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "I don't give a damn what men find attractive. It's unfortunate what we find pleasing to the touch and pleasing to the eye is seldom the same", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "You'd punch me in my belly", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "You'd punch me in my belly", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "I'd smother you. I'd drop it on your right on your face 'til you couldn't breathe", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "my friend retired too", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Not no more", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "You betcha. And if after awhile you don't dig Bora Bora, then we can move over to that place or that place", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "You don't speak Bora Boran either. Besides, Mexican is eas", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "Que hora es", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "What time is it", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": " What time is it", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": " Time for bed. Sweet dream, jellybean", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "It's a little too early in the morning for explosions and war", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "How should I know, you were the one watchin' it", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Uhhh... yes... beside the table drawe", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "Yes, it was on your little kangaroo", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "Yes, it was on your little kangaroo", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": " Well it should be", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "my friend, that was my father's fuckin' watch. You know what my father went through to git me that watch?... I don't wanna get into it right now... but he went through a lot. Now all this other shit, you coulda set on fire, but I specifically reminded you not to forget my father's watch. Now think, did you get it", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "You believe so? You either did, or you didn't, now which one is it", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "Then how come they're all beat up", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": " You were gonna shoot him", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": " It was goo", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "No, they didn't have blueberry pancakes, I had to get buttermilk are you sure you're okay", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "Whose chopper is this", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "Who's Zed", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": ".357", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "Yeah, we were lucky", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "That was... divine intervention. You know what divine intervention is", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "Yeah, man, that's what is means. That's exactly what it means! God came down from Heaven and stopped the bullets", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "Who ya callin'", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "Where's that place", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": "I was just dryin' my hands", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": "You watched me wash 'em", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "I've grasped that, my friend. All I'm doin' is contemplating the", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": "You ain't got no problems, my friend. I'm on the motherfucker. Go back in there, chill them niggers out and wait for The my friend, who should be comin' directly", "qsentId": 74}, {"answer": "You hear that, young lady? Respect. You could lean a lot from those two fine specimens. Respect for one's elders shows character", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 77, "question": "Just because you are a character doesn't mean you have character", "qsentId": 76}, {"answer": "A sewer rat may taste like pumpkin pie.  I'll never know 'cause even if it did, I wouldn't eat the filthy motherfucker. Pigs sleep and root in shit. That's a filthy animal. I don't wanna eat nothin' that ain't got enough sense to disregard its own feces", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 79, "question": "I don't eat dog either", "qsentId": 78}, {"answer": "How about dogs? Dogs eat their own feces", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 81, "question": "Yes, but do you consider a dog to be a filthy animal", "qsentId": 80}, {"answer": "I wouldn't go so far as to call a dog filthy, but they're definitely dirty. But a dog's got personality. And personality goes a long way", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 83, "question": "We'd have to be talkin' 'bout one motherfuckin' charmin' pig. It'd have to be the my friend of pigs", "qsentId": 82}, {"answer": "Do you know that a miracle is", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 85, "question": "What's an act of God", "qsentId": 84}, {"answer": "Please don't! I'm not a hero. I'm just a coffee shop manager. Take anything you want", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 87, "question": "Everybody just be calm and cooperate with them and this will be all over soon", "qsentId": 86}, {"answer": "I'm gonna be okay", "docId": "Pulp-Fiction.txt", "asentId": 89, "question": "I promise", "qsentId": 88}]